http://www.botanicgardens.org/privacy-policy

Skip to main content
Privacy Policy
Collection and Usage of Personal Information
Denver Botanic Gardens (the Gardens), operator of www.botanicgardens.org, recognizes the importance of protecting the privacy of the users of this website and our digital annual report. Except when specifically and knowingly provided by you, the website and/or annual report user, the Gardens collects no personally identifying information about individuals.
As a method of tracking the use of this website, www.botanicgardens.org and our annual report, we may utilize the Web technology known as “cookies,” which enables the Gardens to relate a visitor's use of the Gardens' information to any information that the visitor may have specifically and knowingly provided to the Gardens. Any such voluntarily provided identifying information, if applicable, may be used by the Gardens for editorial, marketing or promotional purposes. Such identifying information, if applicable, will not be transferred to any other party unless otherwise stated at the time of collection.
The Gardens only collects any type of personally identifying information to the extent that it serves our legitimate business purposes, and the Gardens will maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We reserve the right to make changes to this policy at our sole discretion. Such revisions may arise in response to changes in the law, policy, our site or other factors. We encourage you to periodically visit this page to review our most current policy.
Sign up for our e-newsletters!
Subscribe
